<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Authors | Thomas W Rushby</title>
    <link>/authors/</link>
      <atom:link href="/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Authors</description>
    <generator>Source Themes Academic (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020 Tom Rushby</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>/img/bio_pic.jpg</url>
      <title>Authors</title>
      <link>/authors/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/authors/admin/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/admin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thomas Rushby (MSc, PhD) is a researcher within the Sustainable Energy Research Group (Energy and Climate Change Division) at the University of Southampton.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Prior to joining the University of Southampton, Tom spent 10 years working in civil and structural engineering practice before completing a master’s degree in Architecture with a focus on energy, environment and sustainable development.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tom joined the University in 2010, initially working as a Research Engineer on an RCUK funded project – The role of Community-Based Initiatives in Energy Saving – before completing his PhD at the Univeristy of Southampton’s ESRC Doctoral Training Centre (DTC) under the interdisciplinary Energy, Environment and Resilience pathway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;While at the University, Tom has worked on a number of projects with a range of partners, gaining experience in a number of areas including large-scale fieldwork (trial design, implementation and management, trial evaluation) and data analytics and modelling (statistical analysis, microsimulation, spatial microsimulation).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robert Ford</title>
      <link>/authors/robert-ford/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/authors/robert-ford/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
